A.FLORA

9080902615|aflora398@gmail.com|Chennai

ProfileSummary

Entry Level Full Stack Developer with a solid foundation in developing end-to-end web applications. Contributed to develop E-Commerce Webpage. Known for quick learning and adaptability, provided by mastering new programming languages within weeks. Gained experience of developing Micro-Projects.

Skills & Abilities

Skills: Vlookup, Analysis, Problem Solving, Dynamic thinking

Tools: Excel, PPT, Ms Office.

Experience

Graduate Engineering Trainee.

BrakesIndiaPvtLtd, Chennai

03/2023 - 10/2024

- Collaborating with cross-functional teams to improve production efficiency by15%
 through the implementation of lean manufacturing principles and process optimization.
- Conducting root cause an alysis and **implementing corrective actions**, Leading to a 10% reduction in equipment downtime and enhancement in **OEE**.
- Effective utilization of Manpower by standard work combination analysis.

Customer Chat Executive

12/2022 - 02/2023

Redisolve Software Pvt Ltd , Chennai.

Testing Trainee.

08/2019 - 11/2022

Foxconn Hon Hai, Sriperumbudur, Chennai

Education

KingsEngineeringCollege(AnnaUniversity), Chennai. B.E(ECE)

2015-2019.

CGPA-6.8